Guide to the Yale University Building Project Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Project reports, 1994-2003; Accession 2004-A-036
  - Contract for the preliminary architectural services relative to relocation of the Havemeyer House, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Contract with Herbert S. Newman Associates underground auditorium for the Yale Art Gallery, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Contract - Survey on C.S. Space utilization, Taylor, Lieberfeld and Heldman, Inc., 1963 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Contract with the Holtkamp Organ Company for installation of an organ, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Contract with W.J. Megin, Inc. on Yale Center for American Arts and Culture, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Contract - A new Neurology laboratory on the grounds of the VA Hospital, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Contract - Fire protection work SML (VanZelm, Heywood and Shadford), 1969 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Contract - furnish, install and complete smoke detection and fire alarm system at SML, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Contract - modify and expand sprinkler and fire stand-pipe systems at SML (automatic sprinkler), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Contract-Pierson Sage parking extension (C.W. Blakeslee), 1969 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Contract - Renovation of #1 and #2 passenger elevators at SML (F.S. Payne Company), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Contracts for renovation to Anthony Brady Memorial Laboratory-Tomlinson, Hawley and Patterson, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Contract - Sterling Memorial Library Annex (Beinecke) (Tomlinson, Hawley, Patterson), 1969 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Contract - Yale University Branford/Saybrook deferred maintenance and electrical renovation, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Deferred maintenance - temperature control - various buildings - technical assistance etc..., 1982 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Agreement - Derby Boathouse, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Disabilities document, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Expenditure for repairs done by Anthony Brady memorial Laboratory - New Haven Hospital, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Fence Club design, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Agreement for grant between Nathan Cummings Foundation and Yale, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Hill Child Health Center, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - King Cole building, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Agreement: Land records concerning congress Av. bldg overhead pedestrian bridge, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Law library extension - foreign and international law, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Letter contract/lighting service to Sprague Hall and Harkness Hall, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - License to install underground fire and steam service lines, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Maintenance proposal for the Yale Center for British Art and British Studies, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Maintenance service agreement, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Married student dormitory/agreement for retaining walls, site improvements and garage partitions, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Modification and implementation of University's plan for fire safety improvement, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Paved lot, Derby Avenue, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Agreement for permission for the tunnel crossing intersection of High and Wall Street, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Agreement for permission - crossing of the North end of the Cedar Street, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Project - for fibre optic communications link to the Medical School, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Regarding cogeneration and related matters, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Rehabiliation of former Fence Club - 220 York Street, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Contract: Sterling Power Plant chilled water system, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - University Theatre electrical - phase V, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Sloane Physics laboratory work done, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Yale Center for British Arts and Studies, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 58)
- Project management records, circa 2004-2005; Accession 2006-A-095; 24.25; (29 boxes)
  Restricted until 1 Jan 2041.
  - SML Stack Tower and Donor Rooms; 930517-04 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Certif. Of Substantial Completion - Environ, Sciences facility; 931115-01 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Yale ESF Science Center Contract - Attach no. 3; 931115-01 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Yale ESF Science Center Contract - Attach no. 4; 931115-01 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Auth. Y100-10 - Environmental Sciences Facility - GSI Arch.; 931195-10, 1997 July 9 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Auth. Y100-10 - Environmental Sciences Facility - GSI Arch.; 931195-10, 2002 May 9 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Environ. Science Facility - Change Order No 4-7- Linbeck Construction; 931115-10 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Environ. Science Facility - Proposed Change NO. 95-96 - Linbeck Construction; 931115-10 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Environ. Science Facility - Proposed Change NO. 99-101 - Linbeck Construction; 931115-10 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Environ. Science Facility - Proposed Change NO. 103 - Linbeck Construction; 931115-10 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Environ. Science Facility - Proposed Changes NO. 108, 111-112 - Linbeck Construction; 931115-10 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Environ. Science Facility - Proposed Change NO. 113 and 115- Linbeck Construction; 931115-10 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Environ. Science Facility - GSI Arch. Change Auth - Auth No. y100-9; 931115-10 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Environ. Science Facility - Schwarz Change Auth. - Auth No. y100A-3; 931115-10 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Environ. Science Facility - Schwarz Change Auth. - Auth No. y100A-4; 931115-10 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Environ. Science Facility -Contract Schwarz Change Auth. - Auth No. y100A-5; 931115-01 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    General
    Material not received.
  - Environ. Science Facility - Contract Freeman Enterprises; 931115-01 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Environ. Science Facility - Change Order No. 9 - Linbeck Construction; 931115-01 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Environ. Science Facility - Change Order No. 8 - Linbeck Construction; 931115-01 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - P.O. # P 0 3568 PCS - Purchase Order agree. Environ. Science Facility - Linbeck; 931115-01 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Environ Science Facility - Change Order 10-14 - Linbeck Construction; 931115-01 (Box 1, Folder 21-25)
  - Environ. Science Facility - Certification Of Substant. Comple - Linbeck Construction; 931115-10 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - SML Music Library - Change Auth. No. Y103-11; 941031-02 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - PWG, Phase 1 - Schematic Design - Change Auth No. 10; 951011-01 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Hillhouse 27 Ave. Rehab - Petra Construction - Change Order No. 7; 951006-08 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Hillhouse 27 Ave. Rehab - Petra Construction - Change Order No. 8; 951006-08 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Hillhouse 27 Ave. Rehab - Petra Construction - Change Order No. 9; 951006-08 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Hillhouse 27 Ave. Rehab - Petra Construction - Change Order No. 1; 951006-08 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Hillhouse 27 Ave. Rehab - Petra Construction - Change Order No. 2; 951006-08 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Hillhouse 27 Ave. Rehab - Petra Construction - Change Order No. 3; 951006-08 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Hillhouse 27 Ave. Rehab - Petra Construction - Change Order No. 4; 951006-08 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Hillhouse 27 Ave. Rehab - Petra Construction - Change Order No. 5; 951006-08 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Hillhouse 27 Ave. Rehab - Petra Construction - Change Order No. 6; 951006-08 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Hillhouse 27 Ave. Rehab - Certif. Of Substantial Completion - Petra Construction; 951006-08 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Kline Biology Tower - Infrastrct. Improv. Plan - The Hillier Group- Change Auth. No. Y125-3; 990430-01 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Petra Construction Contract - 27 Hillhouse Ave Rehab.; 951006-08 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - SDQ Adaptive Reuse - Certif. Of Substantial Compl. - O'Connell Sons; 960509-01 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - SDQ Adaptive Reuse - O'Connell Sons - Change Order No.10-26; 960509-01 (Box 1, Folder 42-58)
  - SDQ Adaptive Reuse - R.M. Kliment and Frances Halsband Arch - Auth No. Y100-12; 960509-01 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - SDQ Adaptive Reuse - R.M. Kliment and Frances Halsband Arch - Auth No. Y100-13; 960509-01 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - SDQ Adaptive Reuse - R.M. Kliment and Frances Halsband Arch - Auth No. Y100-14; 960509-01 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - SDQ Adaptive Reuse - R.M. Kliment and Frances Halsband Arch - Auth No. Y100-15; 960509-01 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - SDQ Adaptive Reuse - R.M. Kliment and Frances Halsband Arch - Auth No. Y100-16; 960509-01 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - SDQ Adaptive Reuse - R.M. Kliment and Frances Halsband Arch - Auth No. Y100-17; 960509-01 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - SDQ Adaptive Reuse - R.M. Kliment and Frances Halsband Arch - Auth No. Y100-18; 960509-01 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - KCL Roof Replacement - The Hartford Roofing - Change Order No. 1; 960620-01 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Sloane Physics Lab - Paragonn Construction - Change Order No. 11; 961119-03 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Chapel 1156 St. Renovation - Dimeo Contrs. - Change Order No. 33; 970109-02 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - 1156 Chapel St. - Deborah Berke Arch. - Auth No. Y 130-7; 970109-02 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Yale Univ Guidelines for Comprehension Planning study; 970403-01 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Yale Sterling Power Plant - Buckingham Routh Co. - Change Order No. 9-11; 970530-04 (Box 1, Folder 71-73)
  - OML Prospect Renovation - The Hillier Group - Change Auth. No. Y100-6; 970603-01 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - BRBL Basement Renov- Gregg and Wies arch - Change Auth.No. 9; 970722-01 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library Phase IV - Leach Building Co - Change Order No. 03; 970722-01 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library Phase IV - Leach Building Co - Change Order No. 04R; 970722-01 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Welch Hall - The Whiting - Turner Contracting Co. - Change Order No. 1; 970909-02 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Visitor's Center Elm 149 St. Renovation - Leach Building Co. - Change Order No. 06 Final; 971023-01 (Box 1)
  - Visitor's Center Elm 149 St. Renovation - Leach Building Co. - Change Order No. 01; 971023-01 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Visitor's Center Elm 149 St. Renovation - Leach Building Co. - Change Order No. 02; 971023-01 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Visitor's Center Elm 149 St. Renovation - Leach Building Co. - Change Order No. 03R; 971023-01 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Visitor's Center Elm 149 St. Renovation - Leach Building Co. - Change Order No. 04; 971023-01 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Visitor's Center Elm 149 St. Renovation - Leach Building Co. - Change Order No. 05; 971023-01 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Visitor's Center Elm 149 St. Renovation - Certi. Of Substantial Compl. - Leach Building Co.; 971023-01 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Elm 149 St. Renovation - Contract for Construction Phase - Leach Build Co. And Gregg Wies Arch.; 971023-01 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Elm 149 St. Renovation - Contract for Pre- Construction Phase - Leach Build Co. And Gregg Wies Arch.; 971023-01 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Elm 149 St. Renovation - Contract for Arch Services - Gregg Wies Arch.; 971023-01 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Elm 149 St. Renovation - Gregg Wies Arch. - Change Auth. No. Y100A-1; 971023-01 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Elm 149 St. Renovation - Gregg Wies Arch. - Change Auth. No. Y100A-2; 971023-01 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Elm 149 St. Renovation - Gregg Wies Arch. - Change Auth. No. Y100A-3; 971023-01 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Elm 149 St. Renovation - Gregg Wies Arch. - Change Auth. No. Y100A-4r; 971023-01 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - College St. 451 - Certificate of Substantial Completion - Paragon Const.; 980710-01 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - College St. 451 - Paragon Const. - Change Order No. 04 -08; 980710-01 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Davies Mansion Exterior Renovation - F.J. Dahill Change Order No. 1-2; 980206-01 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Davies Mansion Exterior Renovation - F.J. Dahill Change Order No. 3-5; 980206-01 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Davies Mansion Extr Renovation-Contrct for Construction Phase F.J. Dahill Change and Helpern Arch.; 980206-01 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Park St. 211 - Certification Subs. Compl. - Bridgeport Restoration; 980223-24 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Park St. 211 - Bridgeport Restoration - Change Order No. 01-03; 980223-24 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Hillhouse 1 Renovation -J. F. Kelly Co. - Change Order No. 01-04; 980223-33 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Temple St. 370 Renovation - J.F. Kelly CO. - Change Order No. 01-03; 980223-44 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Temple 370 Renovation -J.F. Kelly Co. - Abb. Agree. For Construction Proj.; 980223-44 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Temple 370 Renovation - Allanbrook Benic Czajka LLP - Change Auth. No. Y100A-1 and Y100A-2; 980223-44 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - DL Elevator Modernization- Abb. Agree. For Construction Proj. - Hontz Elavator; 980223-47 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - TD Renovation - Fusco Corp. - Change Order No. 01-03, 05-19; 980223-56 (Box 1, Folder 105-106)
    See also: box 1A, folder 37.
  - TD Renovation - Fusco Corp. - Certification Of Substantial Compl.; 980223-56 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - TD Renovation - Fusco Corp. - Auth. No. for Early release Work # A-1; 980223-56 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - TD Renovation - ATC Assoc.. - Auth. No. Y100-1; 980223-56 (Box 1A, Folder 1)
  - TD Renovation - ATC Assoc.. - Auth. No. Y100-2; 980223-56 (Box 1A, Folder 2)
  - TD Renovation - Peter Gisolfi Assoc. - Auth. No. Y100A-3; 980223-56 (Box 1A, Folder 3)
  - TD Renovation - Peter Gisolfi Assoc. - Auth. No. Y100A-4; 980223-56 (Box 1A, Folder 4)
  - TD Renovation - Peter Gisolfi Assoc. - Auth. No. Y100A-5; 980223-56 (Box 1A, Folder 5)
  - TD Renovation - Fusco and Gisolfi Assoc. - Contract; 980223-56 (Box 1A, Folder 6)
  - CPP New Chiller and Cooling Tower - J.F. Kelly - Cert of Subs. Comple.; 980223-68 (Box 1A, Folder 7)
  - CPP New Chiller and Cooling Tower - The Buckingham Routh Co. - Change Order No. 1; 980223-68 (Box 1A, Folder 8)
  - CPP New Chiller and Cooling Tower - The Buckingham Routh Co. - Change Order Nos. 2-3; 980223-68 (Box 1A, Folder 9)
  - CPP New Chiller and Cooling Tower - The Buckingham Routh Co. - Change Order No. 4; 980223-68 (Box 1A, Folder 10)
  - CPP New Chiller and Cooling Tower - J.F. Kelly - Change Order No. 1; 980223-68 (Box 1A, Folder 11)
  - CPP New Chiller and Cooling Towers - WM Group Eng. - Auth Change No. Y120c-2; 980223-68 (Box 1A, Folder 12)
  - SML Wall St. Buttresses Rehab. - Barr and Barr - Change Order No. 2; 980224-18 (Box 1A, Folder 13)
  - SML Wall St. Buttresses Rehab. - S. B. Richardson and Abbott - Change Auth. No. Y104-6; 980224-18 (Box 1A, Folder 14)
  - ESPLANTS Window Replac. - Fallon Comp. - Abb. Agree.; 980224-19 (Box 1A, Folder 15)
  - ESPLANTS Window Replac. - Fallon Comp. - Certification Of Substantial Compl.; 980224-19 (Box 1A, Folder 16)
  - ESPLANTS Window Replac. - Fallon Comp. - Change Order No. 01-05; 980224-19 (Box 1A, Folder 17)
  - SSS Roof and Masonry Repairs - Bridgeport Restor. Co., Change No. 1; 980224-23 (Box 1A, Folder 18)
  - SSS Roof and Masonry Repairs - Bridgeport Restor. Co., Change No. 2; 980224-23 (Box 1A, Folder 19)
  - SSS Roof and Masonry Repairs - Bridgeport Restor. Co., Change No. 3; 980224-23 (Box 1A, Folder 20)
  - SSS Roof and Masonry Repairs - Bridgeport Restor. Co., Change No. 4; 980224-23 (Box 1A, Folder 21)
  - SSS Roof and Masonry Repairs - Bridgeport Restor. Co., Change No. 5; 980224-23 (Box 1A, Folder 22)
  - SSS Roof and Masonry Repairs - Bridgeport Restor. Co., Change No. 6; 980224-23 (Box 1A, Folder 23)
  - SSS Roof and Masonry Repairs - Bridgeport Restor. Co., Change No. 7; 980224-23 (Box 1A, Folder 24)
  - SSS Roof and Masonry Repairs - Brid. Restor. Co. - Contract; 980224-23 (Box 1A, Folder 25)
  - SSS Roof and Masonry Repairs - Superstructure Eng. Arch. - Change Auth No. Y100A-1; 980224-23 (Box 1A, Folder 26)
  - SSS Roof and Masonry Repairs - Superstructure Eng. Arch. - Change Auth No. Y100A-2; 980224-23 (Box 1A, Folder 27)
  - SSS Roof and Masonry Repairs - Superstructure Eng. Arch. - Change Auth No. Y100A-3; 980224-23 (Box 1A, Folder 28)
  - SSS Roof and Masonry Repairs - Superstructure Eng. Arch. - Change Auth No. Y100A-4; 980224-23 (Box 1A, Folder 29)
  - SSS Roof and Masonry Repairs - Superstructure Eng. Arch. - Change Auth No. Y100A-5; 980224-23 (Box 1A, Folder 30)
  - SSS Roof and Masonry Repairs - Superstructure Eng. Arch. - Change Auth No. Y100A-6; 980224-23 (Box 1)
  - SSS Roof and Masonry Repairs - Superstructures Eng. Arch. form of agreement (limited services); #980224-23, 2001 (Box 1A, Folder 32)
  - 200 York Art History Build - R. Meier and Partners - Change Auth. No. Y100-1; 980223-12 (Box 1A, Folder 33)
  - 200 York Art History Build - Contract for Pre Construction Phase - Meier and Partners - Macomber; 980223-12 (Box 1A, Folder 34)
  - 200 York Art History Build - Contract for Arch. Services - Meier and Partners; 980223-12 (Box 1A, Folder 35)
  - 200 York Art History Build - Abbr. Agr. For Construction Proj. -Standard Demolition; 980223-12 (Box 1A, Folder 36)
  - TD College Renov- Fucso Corp - Change Order 4; 980225-56 (Box 1A, Folder 37)
    See also: box 1, folders 105-106.
  - TD College Renov- Integrated Security Sys. - Change Order Y225-1; 980225-56 (Box 1A, Folder 38)
  - SOM Dining Hall Air Cond. -Abb. Agr. For Construction Proj. -S Monaco, Painting and Build; 980227-01 (Box 1A, Folder 39)
  - Davenport College Renovation - Kiernan Timberlake Assoc. - Change Auth. No. Y100A-a; 980223-77 (Box 1A, Folder 40)
  - Davenport College Renovation - Kiernan Timberlake Assoc.-Contract for Arch.; 980223-77 (Box 1A, Folder 41)
  - Sterling Hall of Medicine I Wing Fire Proct. - Kenneth Boroson and Arch.- Change auth. No. Y100A4; 980327-01 (Box 1B, Folder 1)
  - Y.S.M Sterling Hall of Med. -Fusco Corp.- Change Order No. 6; 980327-01 (Box 1B, Folder 2)
  - YSM Sterling Hall of Medicine - Fusco Corporation - Proposed change order #8; 980327-01, 2002 (Box 1B, Folder 3)
  - LEPH Infrastruture-The Whitting-Turner- Change Order 1; 980417-01 (Box 1B, Folder 4)
  - LEPH Infrastruture-The Whitting-Turner- Change Order 2; 980417-01 (Box 1B, Folder 5)
  - ESH Dorm. Renovation- Dimeo Construction- Change Order Nos. 19 AND 20; 980515-03 (Box 1B, Folder 6)
  - ESH Dorm. Renovation-Baddidge Fac. Construction- Change Order No.1; 980515-03 (Box 1B, Folder 7)
  - Yale Corin. Yacht-F.J. Dahill-Change Order No.1; 980706-01 (Box 1B, Folder 8)
  - Yale Corin. Yacht-F.J. Dahill- Noyes-Vogt Arch. - Contract; 980706-01 (Box 1B, Folder 9)
  - Phelps Hall HVAC and Other Renovation- BVH Eng.- Change Auth. Y120C-2; 980716-01 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Art and Architecture Building Phase II Renovation-Whiting-Turner Contr.-Certification Of Substantial Comple.; 980731-01 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Art and Architecture Building Phase II Renovation-S/L/A/m Collab. - Auth No.Y100A-1; 980731-01 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Art and Architecture Building Phase II Renovation-Whiting-Turner Contr.- Change Order No. 3-Final; 980731-01 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Sterling Hall of Medicine B Wing E Level Fire Prot. - Babbidge Fac. Const. - Change Order No. 1; 980812-04 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Sterling Law Building Phase IV York St. Wing Dorm Renovation - Turner Construction- Change Order No.008; 980819-01 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Sterling Law Building Phase IV York St. Wing Dorm Renovation - Turner Construction- Change Order No.005; 980819-01 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - CMHC Add.- TLB Arch.- Change Auth. No. Y100A-1; 980903-01 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - CMHC Add.- TLB Arch.- Change Auth. No. Y100A-2; 980903-01 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - CMHC Add.- TLB Arch.- Change Auth. No. Y100A-3; 980903-01 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - CMHC Add.- TLB Arch.- Change Auth. No. Y100A-4; 980903-01 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Sterling Hall of Medicine I and WWW Roof Top Combined Exhaust - Babbidge Facil - Change Order No. 2; 981108-01 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Sterling Hall of Medicine I and WWW Roof Top Combined Exhaust - R.G. Vanderweil - Change Auth. Order No. 3; 981108-01 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Hillhouse 56 Renovation- J.F. Kelly- Certification Of Substantial Compl.; 990209-01 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Hillhouse 56 Renovation- J.F. Kelly- Change Order No. 1; 990209-01 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Hillhouse 56 Renovation- J.F. Kelly- Change Order No. 2; 990209-01 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Hillhouse 56 Renovation- J.F. Kelly- Change Order No. 3; 990209-01 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Hillhouse 56 Renovation- J.F. Kelly- Change Order No. 4; 990209-01 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Hillhouse 56 Renovation- J.F. Kelly- Change Order No. 5; 990209-01 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Hillhouse 56 Renovation- J.F. Kelly- Change Order No. 6; 990209-01 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Hillhouse 56 Renovation- Helpern arch. - Change Auth. Order No. Y100A-3; 990209-01 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hillhouse 56 Renovation- Helpern arch. - Change Auth. Order No. Y100A-4; 990209-01 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Kline Biology Tower Infrast. Improv. Plan - Sordoni Skanskaa - Cert of Substantial Compl.; 990430-01 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Kline Biology Tower Infrast. Improv. Plan - Sordoni Skanskaa - Change Order No. 1; 990430-01 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Kline Biology Tower Infrast. Improv. Plan - Sordoni Skanskaa - Change Order No. 2-3; 990430-01 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Kline Biology Tower Infrast. Improv. Plan - Hillier Group - Change Auth. No. Y125-4; 990430-01 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Sterling Hall of Medicine I Wing Fire Proctect. and Corridor Finishes Upgrade - Fusco Corp.- Change Order No. 2; 990525-02 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Sterling Hall of Medicine I Wing Fire Proctect. and Corridor Finishes Upgrade - Fusco Corp.- Change Order No. 3; 990525-02 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Timothy Root House - Leach Building Co. - Change Order 3; 990618-01 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Timothy Root House - Leach Building Co. - Change Order 6; 990618-01 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - YSM Standby Power - Whiting Turner - Change Order No. 2; 990722-01 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Sterling Hall of Medicine C Wing Ast Floor Renovation- Whiting Turner - Change Order No.3; 990930-01 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Farnam Hall Renov 2002 - Whiting Turner- Change No. 1; 990930-02 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Farnam Hall Renov 2002 - Whiting Turner- Change No. 2; 990930-02 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Farnam Hall Renov 2002 - Whiting Turner- Contract Pre-Construction Phase; 990930-02 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Sterling Hall of Medicine Humid. Upgrade- Babbidge Facil. - Change Order 2; 990909-01 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - YSM Standby Power - Whiting Turner - Change Order No. 2; 991026-01 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - YSM Standby Power - Whiting Turner - Change Order No. 2 Final; 991023-01 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - YSM Standby Power - Whiting Turner - Change Order No. 1; 991023-01 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - YSM Standby Power - Whiting Turner - R.G. Vanderweil - Contract Construction Phase; 991023-01 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - MRC Room 131- Babbidge Facil - Change Order No. 1; 991027-01 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - AARF Building B Upgrade - CDS LLC - Change Order No. 2; 991027-02 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - AARF Building B Upgrade - CDS LLC - Change Order No. 3; 991027-02 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - HGS 1st Floor Renovation - Gregg Wies Arch. - Change Auth. No. Y100A-1; 991109-02 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - HGS 1st Floor Renovation - Gregg Wies Arch. - Change Auth. No. Y100A-2; 991109-02 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - HGS 1st Floor Renovation - Gregg Wies Arch. - Change Auth. No. Y100A-3; 991109-02 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - HGS 1st Floor Renovation - Leach Building Co. - Change Order 1; 991109-02 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - HGS 1st Floor Renovation - Leach Building Co. - Change Order 2R2; 991109-02 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - HGS 1st Floor Renovation - Leach Building Co. - Change Order 3 Final; 991109-02 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - HGS 1st Floor Renovation - Leach Building Co. - Change Order 4 Final; 991109-02 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - HGS 1st Floor Renovation - Leach Building Co. - Contract; 991109-02 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - HGS 1st Floor Renovation - Gregg Wies Arch. - Agr. For Arch Services; 991109-02 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Kline Biology Tower, 6th Floor. - Sordoni Skinska - Certification Of Substantial Comple; 991101-01 (Box 2, Folder 27)